err start of season 16 with a new great
partner told me girls they won't deal
Tony I have some fun she's right you
really are amazing to be here it was so
lucky and privileged to offer this
position and super excited to watch a
full season of final tables okay
well listen great final table gonna see
but before that happens we got to make a
little bet I know you're great player
are you a handicapper as well well I do
look the bad thing okay I've divided the
turf and Eric bunch now Jen and Paul
have made a major final table on the WPT
before another is Eric however Eric's
having a fantastic week here at
challenge I got word and their
millionaire maker event he won the PLO
then I don't want to undersell our
underdogs here just because their
longships launched if you get five
points look at the hand the favorites JV
Michael stashing and Josh K and so you
get the honors what are you gonna take
you want to take the favorites at one to
two oil long shots at five to one Tony
what's gonna be well I think you've said
a good
I've decided I'm gonna go with the
favorites today not only do they have 20
million in chips against the underdogs 4
million but Josh pay is a very
experienced player played under the
lights before he has a great seat here
today its current feel like he's the man
to beat O'Laughlin
ok keep in the favor I got the dogs
we'll see what happens let's go to the
felt alright guys I gotta get in on this
action but before we do let's head down
to WPT executive to a director Matt
Savage who has grabbed a quick word
without chip leader Josh K amazing rush
coming into the night's final table how
are you gonna keep the momentum we're
just gonna play the way I played
yesterday you know hopefully everything
works out like it did how's your
experience gonna help you tonight I
think just being through similar
situations before maybe a little bit
more often than the rest might have a
little bit advantage there but you know
you never know what happened alright
good luck tonight
Thanks all right well it looks like
action is about ready to start up there
is a lot
the best
Oh huh what what the oh shit
dad what the fuck are you doing what are
you doing in her bed what are you doing
massager